marketday.com 2013-01-15

# Market Day | Privacy

This is the website of Market Day Corporation and its affiliates ("Market Day") and the privacy policy that pertains to marketday.com, marketdayfundraising.com, and marketdaydirect.com (“Market Day’s websites”). This Privacy Policy does not apply to any website (1) operated by an independent sales consultant of Market Day, including any such site associated with marketdaygourmet.com, or (2) operated by any independent supplier, merchant or retailer referenced on or linked from Market Day’s websites. 

Our postal address is:  
555 W. Pierce Road, Suite 200  
Itasca, IL 60143-2647 

We can be reached via e-mail at [Customer Service](mailto:marketplace1@marketday.com) or you can reach us by telephone at 1.877.MDAPPLE. Questions regarding this policy should be directed to Market Day Corporation. To return to the site, please use the "Back" button on your browser. 

Note: Market Day does not sell, rent or trade consumer mailing lists. 

Market Day Corporation is committed to protecting the privacy of customers of its interactive products and services. The purpose of this privacy policy is to inform you, as a welcome visitor to Market Day’s websites, what kinds of information we may gather about you when you visit these sites, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct, the information. Finally, please note that this policy applies only to Market Day’s websites and not to other companies’ or organizations’ websites to which we link, including the website of any merchant, retailer or independent sales consultant. In addition, this Privacy Policy does not apply to the use or disclosure of information that is collected or obtained by us through means other than through Market Day’s websites. 

information about all market day’s online visitors

Market Day gathers certain web usage information directly and through relationships with online partners. This information helps us manage our Internet business and improve the website experience for our customers. We use web traffic data to measure the effectiveness of our advertising and how visitors use our sites. To do this, we utilize web beacons (a.k.a. clear gifs) and cookies and may also detect and use your internet protocol (IP) address or domain name. The types of information collected include how and when pages on our sites are visited, which products are purchased and how many visitors go to Market Day websites from e-mails we have sent. Cookies also enable the website to remember your user name and password, eliminating the need to re-enter this information each time you visit. By supplementing our records, this information helps us learn things like which pages are most attractive to our visitors, which of our products most interest our customers, and what kinds of promotional offers are most appealing. While we use a marketing company to log some of this information, we control how the data may and may not be used. If you do not want to help us learn how to improve our site, products, offers and marketing strategy, you can “opt-out” of this website analysis tool by clicking here. In addition, if for any reason you do not wish to take advantage of cookies, you may have your browser not accept them. Since cookies are used as part of the online ordering process, if they are disabled on your computer, you will not be able to order products online, and this may also disable some of the features on Market Day’s websites. 

information about mobile features

Market Day may collect usage information related to your use of Mobile Features and services that are available to you via your mobile phone (including text/SMS promotions) and for which you have registered. This information helps us manage our Internet business, learn things like which of our products most interest our customers and what kinds of promotional offers are most appealing. You have the ability to opt-out of your use of the Mobile Features at any time. To do so, simply text "STOP" to Market Day's short code 94543 or opt-out through your "My Account" account preferences. 

information about you

We may specifically ask for information about you when you sign up to use a service or when you order a product. We need certain information such as your name, billing address, mobile phone number and credit card number in order to provide that service or product to you. 

In case you change your mind or wish to update or delete personal information (such as your zip code), we will endeavor to correct, update or remove the personal data you give us. You may change your personal information at any time via the My Account feature on marketday.com or by contacting us at the postal address, e-mail address or phone number mentioned above. 

e-mail addresses

When you register with a Market Day website, we ask for your e-mail address. This information is used to contact you with questions that we may have about your orders or during communication between you and one of our websites, or to provide information or services you request. In addition, you may also “opt-in” and elect to receive promotional information via e-mail from a Market Day website. You can change your mind and “opt-out” from receiving further materials using the process outlined below. 

E-mail addresses may also be collected at times other than registration; for example, in connection with promotions. Certain of Market Day’s websites may from time to time send promotional information to collected e-mail addresses. If you wish to ”opt-out” from receiving such material, please log-in at www.marketday.com and go to “My Account” and select “opt out” or select “unsubscribe” on any of our promotional materials. 

Additionally, if you register with marketday.com your e-mail address will also be provided to the Market Day Chairperson at your school, for the express purpose of enabling the Chairperson to contact you regarding your order or to promote a Market Day sale or other applicable Market Day programs at your school. We do not, however, control how the Market Day Chairperson ultimately uses your e-mail. 

disclosure

We do not disclose information about your individual visits to Market Day’s websites or use of Mobile Features or information that you may give us, such as your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number, to any non-affiliated companies for their personal use. We may disclose your personal identifying information (1) to the Market Day Chairperson at your school as noted above and (2) to Market Day authorized distributorships or alliance partners for the express purposes of enabling that entity to contact you regarding your order or to promote a Market Day sale or other Market Day programs or products. Please note that we do not control how such disclosed data may and may not be used by the receiving parties. 

We may use third party agents to provide certain services that may enhance our site or to help us administer customer promotions, fulfill orders, analyze site use and data, etc. We may provide these agents access to your personal information, including but not limited to your e-mail address, and mobile phone number, if it is necessary for them to perform their services. However, these agents are prohibited from using or disclosing your personal information for any other purpose and are required to keep your information confidential. 

Market Day reserves the right to disclose customer information in special cases, when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, other Market Day website users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. We may disclose personal information without notice to you in response to a subpoena or when we believe in good faith that the law permits it or to respond to an emergency situation. 

Specific areas or pages of our websites may include additional or different provisions relating to collection and disclosure of personal information. In the event of a conflict between such provisions and this Privacy Policy, such specific terms shall control. 

security

Market Day takes reasonable efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of the personal information you provide. However, we will have no liability for disclosure of any information obtained due to errors in transmission or the unauthorized acts of third parties. 

special attention to kids

Market Day understands the concerns of parents for their children’s privacy. We do not knowingly collect personal information about or from children. No information should be submitted to Market Day’s websites by guests under 18 years of age, and guests under 18 years old are not allowed to register at our sites or for promotions. 

market day website use and privacy policy changes

By using Market Day’s websites, you consent to our use of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. As we implement new technology and introduce new services, we may update our Privacy Policy and will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather and how we might use that information. Please check this policy periodically for changes. Your use after any change signifies your acceptance of the changed terms. 

Effective Date: 05/01/2011
